&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：接下来是第五行，因为肯定有一个问题
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Moving on then to line five because there's certainly a question
关于五号线会发生什么。
as to what's gonna happen with line five.
这个主题变量会发生什么？
What's gonna happen with this topic variable?
嗯，它会处理完全一样的，同样的问题。
Well, it's gonna process exactly the same, same questions.
这就是为什么我要教你他们的故事。
That's why I'm teaching you their narrative.
那怎么开始呢？
So how does that start?
嘿范围。
Hey scope of.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：其他类。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Other class.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：其他类。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Other class.
我有一个什么样的推荐人？
I have a what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：目标。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我有一个目标
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Target. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have a target
参考，谢谢。
reference, thank you.
我有一个标识符主题的目标引用。
I have a target reference for the identifier topic.
听说过吗？
Ever heard of it?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：那么我们下一步去哪里？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So where do we go next?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：全局范围。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Global scope.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：全局范围。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A global scope.
我有一个名为topic的变量的目标引用。
I have a target reference for the variable called topic.
听说过吗？
Ever heard of it?
答案是？
And the answer is?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：嗯，我们希望答案是否定的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well we would like for the answer to be no.
答案是否定的似乎是非常合理的。
It seems very reasonable for the answer to be no.
事实上，它似乎有点疯狂，它将永远是除了没有以外的任何东西，但是
In fact it seems somewhat crazy that it would ever be anything other than no but
在这里，我们看到了JavaScript历史上最糟糕的部分之一，即
here we see one of the historical bad parts of JavaScript which is in
对于那些没有做到这一点的人来说，在最初的日子里尽可能地宽恕他们
the early days to be as forgiving as possible for people that didn't
理解语言，他们建立了这个概念的汽车全球的。
understand the language, they instituted this idea of auto global's.
所以如果你试图赋值给一个从未被正式声明过的变量。
So if you try to assign to a variable that's never been formally declared.
一旦你到达全局范围，如果你说嘿，全局范围，
Once you arrive at the global scope, if you say hey, global scope,
我在找这个叫Topic的大理石，听说过吗？
I'm looking for this marble called topic, ever heard of it?
和全局范围，而不是说不，对不起错误，
And the global scope instead of saying nope, sorry error,
全局范围会显示我刚刚为你创建了一个。
the global scope's gonna say I just created one for you.
我是不是很有帮助。
Aren't I helpful.
它会给我们一个红色的大理石，而不是一个蓝色的大理石。
And it's gonna hand us a red marble, not a blue marble.
为什么你认为它只给我们一个红色的大理石，而不是一个蓝色的大理石？
Why do you suppose it only hands us a red marble and not a blue marble?
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：因为它是非全局的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Because it is non globally.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：因为我们现在正在谈论全球范围。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Cuz we're talking to the global scope now.
我们已经忽略了应该正式声明的范围
We've already passed up the scope where that would have been formally declared and
现在我们正在谈论全球范围和
now we're talking to the global scope and
给我们变量的是全局作用域。
it's the global scope that gives us the variable.
你跟我一起吗？
Are you with me?
所以我们创建了一个名为Topic的自动全局
So we've created an auto global called topic which
这听起来很可怕，因为它太可怕了。
that sounds terrible because it is terrible.
但是现在有一个叫做topic的全局变量
But now there's a global variable called topic and
当我们拿回红色大理石并在第五行做作业时，
when we get that red marble back and make the assignment on line five,
现在有一个全局变量，其中有值react，好吗？
there's a global variable now with the value React in it, okay?
&gt；&gt；演讲者4：那么话题就像老师说没有区别一样
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So topic is just like teacher saying there's no difference then
在全球层面上也是如此。
at the global level there too.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不会说没有区别。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I wouldn't say there's no difference.
当然，在编译时创建一个声明，并且
Certainly creating a declaration at compile time and
在运行时动态创建它，有不同之处。
creating it dynamically during the run time, have differences.
存在性能差异和其他种类的事情，但是
There are performance differences and other sorts of things but
机械地说，它们是两个全局变量，在这一点上，好的。
mechanically they are two global variables at this point okay.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：或者沿着这条路，如果你把它包起来，它就会有所不同
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Or down the road if you wrap it around then it will make difference
因为它会再次出现。
because it would pop again up.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，我的意思是如果这不再是全局范围。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I mean if this wasn't the global scope again then.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：但如果稍后再次喷发。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: But if erupted again later on and.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：老师不再是红色的大理石了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Teacher wouldn't be a red marble anymore.
[串音]
[CROSSTALK].
好的，不管你是怎么想的，拿着这个
Okay, regardless of how you wrap your brains around this just take this
特别的外卖，你从来没有在任何情况下故意让汽车
particular takeaway, never ever under any circumstances did you intentionally auto
创建像这样的全局。
create global's like that.
始终声明要使用的变量声明它们
Always declare the variables that you want to use declare them in
无论你需要它们在什么范围内，但不要像这样自动创建它们，是的。
whatever scope you need them in, but don't auto create them like this, yes.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：如果topic equals response是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That would occur also if topic equals react were
在全局范围内，在教师变量下。
in the global scope under variable of teacher.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：没错。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's true.
是的，对当时未声明的变量的任何赋值，
Yeah, any assignment to a variable that is undeclared at that moment,
它不适用于我们有权访问的任何范围，
it is not available to any scope that we have access to,
没有声明到我们有权访问的任何范围。
not declared to any scope we have access to.
任何未声明的变量都将最终创建此自动全局。
Any undeclared variable is going to end up creating this auto global.
现在，发生这种情况的原因是
Now, the reason why that happens
是因为你会注意到这个程序没有在严格模式下运行。
is because you'll notice that this program is not running in strict mode.
稍等片刻，我们将看到何时切换到严格模式，
And in just a moment, we'll see when we flip on strict mode,
它会改变这种行为。
it will change that behavior.
但这是在非严格模式下运行的，有时也称为草率模式。
But this is running in the non-strict mode or sometimes called, sloppy mode.
您应该使用严格模式，如果您使用严格模式，
You should be using strict mode, and if you were using strict mode,
你不会看到这种行为。
you wouldn't see this behavior.
但既然这个代码片段就不是了，这就是发生的事情，
But since this code snip it isn't, that's what happens,
因为我们最终创建了一个名为topic的全局变量，好吗？
as we end up creating a global variable called topic, okay?
然后在函数中执行。
So execution is then done in the function.
我们以与之前相同的方式执行console.log。
We execute console.log the same way as we have before.
执行移动到第11行。
Execution moves to line 11.
第11行的执行是如何工作的？
How does the execution of line 11 work?
嘿，我们得对着一个范围说话，对，和以前一样的谈话，同样的叙述。
Hey, we gotta talk to a scope, right, same conversation as before, same narrative.
所以嘿，全球范围，嘿红桶。
So hey, global scope, hey red bucket.
我有一个什么样的推荐人？
I have a what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：源引用。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Source reference.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：对名为？的变量的源引用？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A source reference to a variable called?
老师。老师。
Teacher. Teacher.
听说过吗？答案是？
Ever heard of it? And the answer is?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yes.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我们去拿大理石，看看它的价值。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we go get that marble and we look for its value.
它有什么价值？
And what value does it have?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：suzy。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Suzy.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它有Suzy。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It has Suzy.
记得吗？因为四号线，
Remember? Because of line four,
我们分配给一个红色的大理石。
we assigned to a red marble.
我们已经覆盖了该变量中的值。
We've overwritten the value in that variable.
它不是一个单独的变量，也不是一个单独的大理石。
It's not a separate variable, not a separate marble.
好的，第12行，那么第12行是如何执行的？
Okay, line 12 then, how does line 12 execute?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：嘿，全球范围。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Hey global scope.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，全球范围内，我有一个？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey global scope, I have a?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：来源。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：来源参考？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Source. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Source reference for?
主题。话题，你们是这方面的专家，非常好。
Topic. Topic, you're experts at this, very good.
听说过主题吗？
Ever heard of topic?
全球范围内会说？
And global scope's gonna say?
这是你的红色大理石。
Here's your red marble.
当我们看到红色大理石的价值时，它会说？
And when we look at the value in the red marble it's gonna say?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：反应。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: React.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：反应，反应。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: React, react.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：所以如果第11行跑在第9行之前，老师仍然是最高的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So if line 11 ran before line 9, teacher would still be top.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：再说一遍，我很抱歉？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Say that again I'm sorry?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：所以如果线路11实际上在线路8中。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So if line 11 was actually in line 8.
&gt；&gt；kyle simpson：我想你说的是12号线？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think you're talking about line 12?
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：我说的是第11行。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I'm talking about line 11.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，那么
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so
如果第11行在第8行，那么老师会说Kyle，正确。
if line 11 was on line 8 then teacher would say Kyle, correct.
如果线路12在线路8上会发生什么？
What would happen if line 12 was on line 8?
不会有标识符，对吧？
There would be no identifier, right?
我们将在下一张幻灯片中看到这种情况。
We'll see that case in the next slide.
但是在第12行有一个标识符，因为
But there is an identifier on line 12 because
函数other Class auto通过分配给未声明的变量来创建它。
the function otherClass auto created it by assigning to a non-declared variable.